KIMI K3 IS NOT A NORMAL MODEL
@ashen_one  •  FULL VIDEO CLIPPED BY PROMETHEUS
The Chinese have done it again, but this time they're coming for our fable five tokens
and credits.
No, I'm joking, so K3, Kimi K3 came out this week, and it is supposed to be the world's
strongest open weight model ever, even beating fable five on certain benchmarks.
But as you know on this channel, we don't really listen to these benchmarks because
we can't even read to begin with.
We only care about certain tests, like how good is it?
Like how fast is it?
How cost effective is it?
How does it compare to other leading models, like 5.6 Sol, or even Opus 4.8?
Because fable five, even...
And of course, how well can it recreate Minecraft, which we'll go over later in this
video.