OPEN MODELS ARE CATCHING UP FAST
@ashen_one  •  FULL VIDEO CLIPPED BY PROMETHEUS
But it's basically claiming to be damn near as good as fable five, if not better than
5.6 sole and Opus 4.8 on a lot of different benchmarks and even other people who are
smarter than me and actually do know how to read, they're saying, oh, we're in for some
trouble.
Since when did like Chinese open weight models get so strong, even bridge mine, the goat.
He's saying that Kimi K3 beats fable five on his own personal benchmark of like making
a lava lamp.
So look at this.
This lava lamp is prettier.
And even this guy, David Sacks, he's from the all-in podcast, he's also super smart guy.
And he was saying, oh, oh, China not only has released such a banger model time and time
after again, but it's also now almost as smart, maybe even smarter than our American smartest
models, even right here, because right here, arena AI is saying that Kimi K3 is smarter
than fable five by not just like 1% but maybe I don't know, three to four, 5% and not
just which is a crazy thing to claim because fable five is supposed to be so strong.
It's so smart and so capable, ultra on level AI that they can't even give it to the public.
Just yesterday is when they announced that they're going to keep fable five on the monthly
subscriptions for clawed code users.